dailyscribe.com 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy for DailyScribe

Most Recent

|  | 

Home > Privacy Policy for DailyScribe 

At DailyScribe, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit DailyScribe, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. The DailyScribe Web site is owned and operated by IcoLogic, Inc.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us though our Contact Page

**Gathering of Information  
**  
**Voluntary Submission:** DailyScribe does not collect personally identifying information about any individual web site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, when a visitor comes to DailyScribe to read an article, we do not ask for nor do we collect personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies:** A cookie is a data file that certain Web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. DailyScribe uses cookies solely to track user traffic patterns throughout the DailyScribe Web site. We use this data on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user.

Most Web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our Web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site. We also use third party advertisements on DailyScribe to help support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and various browser options you may have installed on your web browser. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

**Log Files & Browser Level Information: **As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your Internet Service Provider, the web browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. If available, we may also record referral information to determine how you were referred to our site from external web sites.

**Use of Information:** Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our Web site. We achieve this goal by, among other things, providing interactive communications such as our welcome email, and developing future products and services based on your interests. To develop content targeted to your interests, we use aggregated user information to determine which areas of our Web site users prefer based upon traffic to those areas.

DailyScribe derives the majority of its revenue from advertising. In order to attract and retain advertisers we may use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. We do not disclose personally identifying information about our users to these parties.

DailyScribe may also disclose information about our users when we believe, in good faith, that the disclosure is required by law. Web Form contact information is monitored on SearchWarp to help detect and deter unwanted email messages.

When you are on an area of DailyScribe and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with DailyScribe as well as business partners and vendors providing hosting and other services for DailyScribe. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. These parties, as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements, may set their own cookies.

In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by our users as part of an advertiser promotion online may be provided directly to advertisers.

Please be aware that DailyScribe sponsors, advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and Web sites linked to DailyScribe are not covered by this privacy statement. DailyScribe users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.

Kids under 13: Do not send any information about yourself to us, including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

**Additional Information:** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**How to Contact Us:** If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us though our Contact Page

This statement may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**Definitions:**

**IP address:** Every computer connected to the Internet has a numeric address called an “IP address." This may or may not correspond uniquely to a particular computer. In some cases, IP addresses can be resolved to domain names, which may indicate a site visitor's Internet service provider, employer, university, etc. As part of its database analysis DailyScribe resolves IP addresses to domain names.

**Browser type:** A user’s browser is a software program running on a computer that allows users to access documents on the World Wide Web. Browsers can be either text or graphic. They read HTML coded pages that reside on a server and interpret the coding into what the user sees as Web pages. Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer are examples of Web browsers. Browser type typically discloses hardware platform, operating system, and browser software and version.

**Referrer:** The referrer is the URI of the Internet resource or page that causes a browser to request a page or image from DailyScribe servers.

|  | 

Most Popular
